Marc Brown Papers MS148
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Arthur audiovisual material, 1994 -- 2006; 1995 -- 2001; MS148.002; 0.25 Linear Feet; 552 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - 304: Background blues, 1998; MS148.002.341.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 341)
  - 304: And now let's talk to some kids, 1998; MS148.002.341.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 341)
  - 305: The chips are down, 1998; MS148.002.342.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 342)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-010#00020-00028.
  - 305: Revenge of the chip, 1998; MS148.002.342.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 342)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-010#00041-00048.
  - 305: The chips are down, 1998; MS148.002.343.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 343)
  - 305: Revenge of the chip, 1998; MS148.002.343.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 343)
  - 306: Binky rules, 1998; MS148.002.344.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 344)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-009#00023-00031.
  - 306: Meet Binky, 1998; MS148.002.344.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 344)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-010#00029-00034.
  - 306: Binky rules, 1998; MS148.002.345.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 345)
  - 306: Meet Binky, 1998; MS148.002.345.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 345)
  - 307: Arthur rides the bandwagon, 1998; MS148.002.346.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 346)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-009#00051-00058.
  - 307: Dad's dessert dilemma, 1998; MS148.002.346.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 346)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00009-00016.
  - 307: Arthur rides the bandwagon, 1998; MS148.002.347.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 347)
  - 307: Dad's dessert dilemma, 1998; MS148.002.347.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 347)
  - 308: Popular girls, 1998; MS148.002.348.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 348)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-010#00055-00059.
  - 308: Buster's growing grudge, 1998; MS148.002.348.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 348)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00030-00038.
  - 308: Popular girls, 1998; MS148.002.349.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 349)
  - 308: Buster's growing grudge, 1998; MS148.002.349.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 349)
  - 309: Arthur's treasure hunt, 1999; MS148.002.350.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 350)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-010#00012-00020.
  - 309: The return of the king, 1999; MS148.002.350.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 350)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00045-00051.
  - 309: Arthur's treasure hunt, 1999; MS148.002.351.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 351)
  - 309: The return of the king, 1999; MS148.002.351.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 351)
  - 310: Attack of the turbo Tibbles, 1999; MS148.002.352.00001 (Box 352)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-010#00066-00068 and MS148/001-011#00001-00002.
  - 310: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy, 1999; MS148.002.352.00002 (Box 352)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00023-00030.
  - 311: Double Tibble trouble, 1999; MS148.002.353.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 353)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00012-00019.
  - 311: Arthur's almost live not real music festival, 1999; MS148.002.353.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 353)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00019-00028.
  - 311: Double Tibble trouble, 1999; MS148.002.354.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 354)
  - 311: Arthur's almost live not real music festival, 1999; MS148.002.354.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 354)
  - 312: What scared Sue Ellen?, 1999; MS148.002.355.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 355)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00058-00065.
  - 312: Clarissa is cracked, 1999; MS148.002.355.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 355)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00070-00076.
  - 312: What scared Sue Ellen?, 1999; MS148.002.356.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 356)
  - 312: Clarissa is cracked, 1999; MS148.002.356.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 356)
  - 312: What scared Sue Ellen?, 1999; MS148.002.357.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 357)
  - 312: Clarissa is cracked, 1999; MS148.002.357.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 357)
  - 313: Arthur's dummy disaster, 1999; MS148.002.358.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 358)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00017-00022.
  - 313: Francine and the feline, 1999; MS148.002.358.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 358)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00039-00044.
  - 313: Arthur's dummy disaster, 1999; MS148.002.359.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 359)
  - 313: Francine and the feline, 1999; MS148.002.359.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 359)
  - 313: Arthur's dummy disaster, 1999; MS148.002.360.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 360)
  - 313: Francine and the feline, 1999; MS148.002.360.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 360)
  - 314: Mom and Dad have a great big fight, 1999; MS148.002.361.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 361)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00066-00070.
  - 314: D.W.'s perfect wish, 1999; MS148.002.361.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 361)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00001-00005.
  - 314: Mom and Dad have a great big fight, 1999; MS148.002.362.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 362)
  - 314: D.W.'s perfect wish, 1999; MS148.002.362.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 362)
  - 315: Arthur and D.W. clean up, 1999; MS148.002.363.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 363)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00005-00011.
  - 315: The long, dull winter, 1999; MS148.002.363.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 363)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-011#00052-00058.
  - 315: Arthur and D.W. clean up, 1999; MS148.002.364.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 364)
  - 315: The long, dull winter, 1999; MS148.002.364.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 364)
  - 315: Arthur and D.W. clean up, 1999; MS148.002.365.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 365)
  - 315: The long, dull winter, 1999; MS148.002.365.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 365)
  - 401: D.W.'s library card, 1999; MS148.002.366.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 366)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00064-00072.
  - 401: Arthur's big hit, 1999; MS148.002.366.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 366)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00073 and MS148/001-013#00001-00007.
  - 401: D.W.'s library card, 1999; MS148.002.367.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 367)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00064-00072.
  - 401: Arthur's big hit, 1999; MS148.002.367.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 367)
  - 402: Hide and snake, 1999; MS148.002.368.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 368)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00049-00059.
  - 402: Muffy's new best friend, 1999; MS148.002.368.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 368)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00045-00051.
  - 402: Hide and snake, 1999; MS148.002.369.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 369)
  - 402: Muffy's new best friend, 1999; MS148.002.369.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 369)
  - 403: Buster's breathless, 1999; MS148.002.370.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 370)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00016-00027.
  - 403: The fright stuff, 1999; MS148.002.370.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 370)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00029-00037.
  - 403: Buster's breathless, 1999; MS148.002.371.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 371)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00016-00027.
  - 403: The fright stuff, 1999; MS148.002.371.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 371)
  - 404: The contest, 1999; MS148.002.372.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 372)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-012#00037-00048.
  - 404: Prove it, 1999; MS148.002.372.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 372)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00062-00072.
  - 404: The contest, 1999; MS148.002.373.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 373)
  - 404: Prove it, 1999; MS148.002.373.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 373)
  - 405: The blizzard, 1999; MS148.002.374.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 374)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00004-00012. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-142#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-546#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-375#00001 and MS148/002-376#00001.
  - 405: The rat who came to dinner, 1999; MS148.002.374.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 374)
    This date is approximate. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00027-00035.
  - 405: The blizzard, 1999; MS148.002.375.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 375)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00004-00012. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-142#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-546#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-374#00001 and MS148/002-376#00001.
  - 405: The rat who came to dinner, 1999; MS148.002.375.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 375)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00027-00035.
  - 405: The blizzard, 1999; MS148.002.376.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 376)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00004-00012. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-142#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-546#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-374#00001 and MS148/002-375#00001.
  - 405: The rat who came to dinner, 1999; MS148.002.376.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 376)
  - 406: D.W. tale spins, 1999; MS148.002.377.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 377)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00031-00039.
  - 406: Prunella gets it twice, 1999; MS148.002.377.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 377)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00008-00015.
  - 406: D.W. tale spins, 1999; MS148.002.378.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 378)
  - 406: Prunella gets it twice, 1999; MS148.002.378.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 378)
  - 407: Binky Barnes, wingman, 1999; MS148.002.379.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 379)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00021-00031.
  - 407: To beat or not to beat, 1999; MS148.002.379.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 379)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00052-00063.
  - 407: Binky Barnes, wingman, 1999; MS148.002.380.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 380)
  - 407: To beat or not to beat, 1999; MS148.002.380.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 380)
  - 407: Binky Barnes, wingman, 1999; MS148.002.381.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 381)
  - 407: To beat or not to beat, 1999; MS148.002.381.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 381)
  - 408: 1001 dads, 1999; MS148.002.382.00001 (Box 382)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00073-00082. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-141#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-545#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-383#00001.
  - 408: Prunella's prediction, 1999; MS148.002.382.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 382)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00083-00089 and MS148/001-014#00001-00003. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-141#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-545#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-383#00002.
  - 408: 1001 dads, 1999; MS148.002.383.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 383)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00073-00082. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-141#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-545#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-382#00001.
  - 408: Prunella's prediction, 1999; MS148.002.383.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 383)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00083-00089 and MS148/001-014#00001-00003. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-141#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-545#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-382#00002.
  - 409: What is that thing?, 1999; MS148.002.384.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 384)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00013-00020. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-142#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-546#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-385#00001 and MS148/002-386#00001.
  - 409: Buster's best behavior, 1999; MS148.002.384.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 384)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00040-00049. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-145#00001 and MS148/002-547#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-146#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-385#00002 and MS148/002-386#00002.
  - 409: What is that thing?, 1999; MS148.002.385.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 385)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00013-00020. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-142#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-546#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-384#00001 and MS148/002-386#00001.
  - 409: Buster's best behavior, 1999; MS148.002.385.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 385)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00040-00049. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-145#00001 and MS148/002-547#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-146#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-384#00002 and MS148/002-386#00002.
  - 409: What is that thing?, 1999; MS148.002.386.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 386)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00013-00020. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-142#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-546#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-384#00001 and MS148/002-385#00001.
  - 409: Buster's best behavior, 1999; MS148.002.386.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 386)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00040-00049. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-145#00001 and MS148/002-547#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-146#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-384#00002 and MS148/002-385#00002.
  - 410: My music rules, 1999; MS148.002.387.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 387)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00050-00057. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-547#00002 and MS148/002-145#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-146#00002 and MS148/002-129#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-388#00001.
  - 410: That's a baby show!, 1999; MS148.002.387.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 387)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-013#00036-00044.
  - 410: My music rules, 1999; MS148.002.388.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 388)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00050-00057. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-547#00002 and MS148/002-145#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-146#00002 and MS148/002-129#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-387#00001.
  - 410: That's a baby show!, 1999; MS148.002.388.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 388)
  - 501: Arthur and the big riddle, 2000; MS148.002.389.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 389)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-015#00022-00034.
  - 501: Double dare, 2000; MS148.002.389.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 389)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-015#00014-00021.
  - 501: Arthur and the big riddle, 2000; MS148.002.390.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 390)
  - 501: Double dare, 2000; MS148.002.390.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 390)
  - 502: Kids are from Earth, parents are from Pluto, 2000; MS148.002.391.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 391)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00058-00069.
  - 502: Nerves of steal, 2000; MS148.002.391.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 391)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-015#00033-00046.
  - 502: Kids are from Earth, parents are from Pluto, 2000; MS148.002.392.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 392)
  - 502: Nerves of steal, 2000; MS148.002.392.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 392)
  - 503: It's a no-brainer, 2000; MS148.002.393.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 393)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-014#00069-00077 and MS148/001-015#00001-00003.
  - 503: The shore thing, 2000; MS148.002.393.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 393)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-015#00004-00013.
  - 503: It's a no-brainer, 2000; MS148.002.394.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 394)
  - 503: The shore thing, 2000; MS148.002.394.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 394)
  - 504: The world record, 2000; MS148.002.395.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 395)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-016#00036-00048.
  - 504: The cave, 2000; MS148.002.395.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 395)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-016#00025-00037.
  - 504: The world record, 2000; MS148.002.396.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 396)
  - 504: The cave, 2000; MS148.002.396.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 396)
  - 505: The lousy week, 2000; MS148.002.397.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 397)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-016#00002-00012.
  - 505: You are Arthur, 2000; MS148.002.397.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 397)
    This date is approximate. RT; 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-016#00049-00061.
  - 505: The lousy week, 2000; MS148.002.398.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 398)
  - 505: You are Arthur, 2000; MS148.002.398.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 398)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-016#00049-00061.
  - 506: The election, 2000; MS148.002.399.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 399)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-016#00013-00024.
  - 506: Francine goes to war, 2000; MS148.002.399.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 399)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-015#00058-00069 and MS148/001-016#00001.
  - 506: The election, 2000; MS148.002.400.00001 (Box 400)
  - 506: Francine goes to war, 2000; MS148.002.400.00002 (Box 400)
  - 506: The election, 2000; MS148.002.401.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 401)
    This date is approximate. RT; 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-016#00013-00024.
  - 506: Francine goes to war, 2000; MS148.002.401.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 401)
  - 507: Sleep no more, 2000; MS148.002.402.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 402)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-016#00060-00064 and MS148/001-017#00001-00010.
  - 507: Pet peeved, 2000; MS148.002.402.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 402)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-017#00022-00036.
  - 507: Sleep no more, 2000; MS148.002.403.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 403)
  - 507: Pet peeved, 2000; MS148.002.403.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 403)
  - 508: The last of Mary Moo Cow, 2000; MS148.002.404.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 404)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-015#00047-00059.
  - 508: Bitzi's beau, 2000; MS148.002.404.00002 (Box 404)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-017#00011-00022.
  - 508: The last of Mary Moo Cow, 2000; MS148.002.405.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 405)
  - 508: Bitzi's beau, 2000; MS148.002.405.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 405)
  - 509: Just desserts, 2000; MS148.002.406.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 406)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-017#00049-00059.
  - 509: The big dig, 2000; MS148.002.406.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 406)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00001-00014.
  - 509: Just desserts, 2000; MS148.002.407.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 407)
  - 509: The big dig, 2000; MS148.002.407.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 407)
  - 510: Arthur's family feud, 2000; MS148.002.408.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 408)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00014-00030.
  - 510: Muffy gets mature, 2000; MS148.002.408.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 408)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-017#00037-00050.
  - 510: Arthur's family feud, 2000; MS148.002.409.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 409)
  - 510: Muffy gets mature, 2000; MS148.002.409.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 409)
  - 601: Sue Ellen gets her goose cooked, 2001; MS148.002.410.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 410)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00037-00042.
  - 601: Best of the nest, 2001; MS148.002.410.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 410)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00043-00047. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-548#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-411#00002.
  - 601: Sue Ellen gets her goose cooked, 2001; MS148.002.411.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 411)
  - 601: Best of the nest, 2001; MS148.002.411.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 411)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00043-00047. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-548#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-410#00002.
  - 602: Arthur plays the blues, 2001; MS148.002.412.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 412)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00054-00058. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-549#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-413#00001.
  - 602: Buster's sweet success, 2001; MS148.002.412.00002; WGBH (Firm) (Box 412)
    This date is approximate. RT: 28:46. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-018#00059-00065. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-549#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-413#00002.